<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://seeqsupply.com/blogs/blog.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://seeqsupply.com/blogs/blog"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://seeqsupply.com/blogs/blog/tagged/featured-in.atom"/>
  <title>SEEQ  - SEEQ Clear Protein</title>
  <updated>2025-07-31T14:37:49-05:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>SEEQ </name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://seeqsupply.com/blogs/blog/find-your-greatness-seeq</id>
    <published>2024-12-10T13:29:20-06:00</published>
    <updated>2025-07-24T09:57:13-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://seeqsupply.com/blogs/blog/find-your-greatness-seeq"/>
    <title>Find Your Greatness - SEEQ</title>
    <author>
      <name>LEO Store2018 Admin</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p data-mce-fragment="1">We were sick of the boring traditional thick and milky protein options on the market, so we started working with food scientists and formulators to create a protein that has a juice-like consistency, and SEEQ was born. Our customers are dominantly in the fitness space; however, we are positioning ourselves in the market as an approachable brand to all active people and are not just singling out the heavy gym-goers.</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"> </p>
<h3 id="tell-us-about-yourself">Tell us about yourself</h3>
<p>I've been an entrepreneur at heart since I was in high school. From flipping items on Facebook and eBay to going door-to-door selling exterior painting services, I've always had the passion to be my own boss and to make things happen. Previously to SEEQ, I owned a small marketing agency where I was focused on driving the digital marketing goals of small businesses in MN. I met Ben Zaver, the Founder of SEEQ when he interned at a marketing agency that I was already working at.</p>
<p>After his internship ended, I didn't really hear from him until one day; he stopped by our office in Minneapolis. He gave us all samples of this juice-like protein. I was super jacked to see someone go after their dream and start their entrepreneurial journey. I already have a passion for being an entrepreneur; I extended my help, and he gladly took it. He worked on it two years before we launched; I jumped on board about six months into his journey. We officially launched in October 2021, and we've seen explosive growth on social media. We are both full-time on this journey, and the thing that motivates us each day to continue what we are doing is seeing the community that we are slowly building. It's one thing just to sell a product, but it's another thing to build a brand and a culture that people want to be a part of.</p>
<h3 id="whats-your-biggest-accomplishment-as-a-business-owner">What's your biggest accomplishment as a business owner?</h3>
<p>I'd have to say the thing that has excited us the most would have to be selling out our new flavor in just 6 hours. Seeing over 1000 people on the site at one time and having thousands of orders come in just the first 15 minutes was hard for us to wrap our heads around. We're so grateful for our community and everyone that has supported us so far.</p>
<h3 id="whats-one-of-the-hardest-things-that-come-with-being-a-business-owner">What's one of the hardest things that come with being a business owner?</h3>
<p>Burnout is real, and many entrepreneurs and marketers can relate to that. Nobody tells you about manufacturing agreements or how to negotiate and all the other little things that come with owning a business. Although that is difficult, it's also really exciting to us that we now have more experience under our belt for the next thing that we start.</p>
<h3 id="what-are-the-top-tips-youd-give-to-anyone-looking-to-start-run-and-grow-a-business-today">What are the top tips you'd give to anyone looking to start, run and grow a business today?</h3>
<ol>
<li>Don't wait till you're ready or for it to be perfect; otherwise, you'll always be waiting. Start now with what you have, knowing that things will change.</li>
<li>Connect with people that you want to learn from and look up too often, at least one new conversation each week. There's a reason why people always say your network is your net worth.</li>
<li>Focus more on brand and community, overselling your product. When you focus on the people buying your product instead of just trying to sell your product, you seem more authentic, and people will gravitate towards that.</li>
</ol>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://seeqsupply.com/blogs/blog/maple-grove-grad-seeing-growth-with-unique-protein-shake-business</id>
    <published>2024-12-10T13:27:30-06:00</published>
    <updated>2025-07-24T09:57:12-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://seeqsupply.com/blogs/blog/maple-grove-grad-seeing-growth-with-unique-protein-shake-business"/>
    <title>Maple Grove grad seeing growth with unique protein shake business</title>
    <author>
      <name>LEO Store2018 Admin</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<div class="subscriber-preview" data-mce-fragment="1">
<p data-mce-fragment="1">hen Maple Grove alumnus Ben Zaver graduated from college during the pandemic shutdown, he didn’t know it would give him plenty of time to pursue a business dream opportunity.</p>
</div>
<div class="subscriber-preview" data-mce-fragment="1">
<p data-mce-fragment="1">Born and raised in Plymouth, he attended elementary and middle school in Maple Grove and then went on to graduate from Maple Grove Senior High School.</p>
</div>
<div class="subscriber-only" data-mce-fragment="1">
<p data-mce-fragment="1">In May 2020, Zaver graduated from Minnesota State University, Mankato, with a degree in mechanical engineering. “I was at a job interview in Arizona during spring break when COVID hit and I finished college online back home in Plymouth,” he said.</p>
</div>
<div id="tncms-region-article_instory_top" class="tncms-region hidden-print" data-mce-fragment="1">
<div id="tncms-block-2644836" class="tncms-block" data-mce-fragment="1">
<div data-type="float" data-mce-fragment="1" s2nplayer="" k-enuo38ij=""></div>
</div>
</div>
<div class="subscriber-only" data-mce-fragment="1">
<p data-mce-fragment="1">The pandemic forced him to stay at home, but this allowed Zaver to start his own protein company. His company, SEEQ, started with a basic idea.</p>
<div class="subscriber-only">
<p>“I always hated the taste and texture of the typical thick and milky protein shakes and thought there had to be a better option,” he said.</p>
</div>
<div class="subscriber-only">
<p>Zaver did some research and found a manufacturer that invented an ingredient that was able to make the consistency of protein shakes more like a juice. “This allowed us to make refreshing fruity flavors like strawberry and mango pineapple possible,” he said. “[The] fruity flavors are a lot more refreshing after a workout and don’t leave you feeling bloated. We like to think we make protein shakes that people actually look forward to drinking.”</p>
</div>
<div class="subscriber-only">
<p>During the pandemic quarantine, Zaver said he had a lot of time on his hands and spent a lot of it doing research and networking as well as learning some programming, website development, packaging and all kinds of other things that go into starting a product.</p>
</div>
<div class="subscriber-only">
<p>“After we found the right [manufacturer], I subjected my friends and family to hundreds of taste tests until we got the flavors and consistency just right,” he said. “There was a lot of trial and error. That just led me to do a lot more of that type of things on my own.”</p>
</div>
<div class="subscriber-only">
<p>His parents Steve and Kate said COVID changed everyone’s plans. “That’s what I call a silver lining,” Kate Zaver said. “So many nights of family walks, movie nights and home projects were great, but I knew Ben would get bored after graduating from college. He had been thinking of this protein idea and once he shared his vision, it was on.”</p>
</div>
<div class="subscriber-only">
<p>They said it was hard to watch him struggle during setbacks, but Zaver’s optimism and kept him forging ahead.</p>
</div>
</div>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://seeqsupply.com/blogs/blog/seeq-protein-powder-company-co-founded-by-sioux-falls-woman-gains-popularity-through-tiktok</id>
    <published>2024-12-10T13:24:53-06:00</published>
    <updated>2025-07-24T09:57:10-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://seeqsupply.com/blogs/blog/seeq-protein-powder-company-co-founded-by-sioux-falls-woman-gains-popularity-through-tiktok"/>
    <title>SEEQ protein powder company, co-founded by Sioux Falls woman, gains popularity through TikTok</title>
    <author>
      <name>LEO Store2018 Admin</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p class="gnt_ar_b_p" data-mce-fragment="1">Hannah Perez always had an interest in entrepreneurship. She grew up in Sioux Falls and graduated from Roosevelt High School in 2016, which is when her passion for creating a business really began.</p>
<p class="gnt_ar_b_p" data-mce-fragment="1">In high school, Perez enjoyed reselling knock-off Yeezy boots, which were very popular at the time, and that eventually led her to becoming the co-founder of SEEQ, a clear protein powder company that does its market exclusively on TikTok.</p>
<p class="gnt_ar_b_p" data-mce-fragment="1">Perez initially went to college in Mankato, Minnesota, for elementary education, but she soon switched her major to marketing when she realized her true desire was to go into business.</p>
<p class="gnt_ar_b_p" data-mce-fragment="1"> </p>
<p class="gnt_ar_b_p">One of her internships, called College Works Painting, involved starting a company, building a team and going door to door selling paint. </p>
<p class="gnt_ar_b_p">“That really created my drive and let me know that I am capable of doing something that’s hard and just-out-of-left-field, like selling paint,” said Perez. “I’m not passionate about paint, but if I can sell that, I’ll be able to do anything.”</p>
<p class="gnt_ar_b_p">After graduating, Perez started working at a digital marketing startup called The Social Butterfly in Minneapolis, where she met Ben Zaver, who came on as an intern. </p>
<figure class="gnt_em gnt_em_img gnt_em_img__inset"></figure>
<p class="gnt_ar_b_p">Eventually, The Social Butterfly shut down and Perez started her own digital marketing agency, Awake Social, but not before Zaver came and pitched his new protein powder, hoping to start it as a business. Perez jumped on the idea, and the two spent the next year developing the company before launching SEEQ in October 2021. </p>
<p class="gnt_ar_b_p">“I know how to manage a business. I am really big into fitness, so this was right up my alley,” said Perez. Zaver’s parents loaned them initial investment money for that first round of inventory and things took off after that.</p>
<p class="gnt_ar_b_p">“Without them, we wouldn’t be here, so shout-out to the Zaver family,” said Perez. </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://seeqsupply.com/blogs/blog/how-this-protein-powder-startup-is-using-tiktok-to-sell-out-inventory-faster-than-it-can-restock</id>
    <published>2024-12-10T13:16:45-06:00</published>
    <updated>2025-07-24T09:57:09-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://seeqsupply.com/blogs/blog/how-this-protein-powder-startup-is-using-tiktok-to-sell-out-inventory-faster-than-it-can-restock"/>
    <title>How this protein-powder startup is using TikTok to sell out inventory faster than it can restock</title>
    <author>
      <name>LEO Store2018 Admin</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8"><span data-mce-fragment="1"></span><span data-mce-fragment="1"></span><span data-mce-fragment="1">Ben Zaver was a few months away from graduating with a mechanical engineering degree when the pandemic started.<br data-mce-fragment="1"><br data-mce-fragment="1">Rather than begin his engineering career, Zaver used the time spent sheltering at home to develop a whey protein powder that was clear and refreshing, unlike the chunky and unpleasant-tasting powders that dominate the market. <br data-mce-fragment="1"><br data-mce-fragment="1">After taking a year-and-a-half to perfect the formula, and teach himself how to run a business, Zaver along with Co-founder Hannah Perez launched Seeq in October 2021. In the ensuing months, the pair have posted $800,000 in sales solely by marketing on TikTok.<br data-mce-fragment="1"><br data-mce-fragment="1">Zaver's account on the social platform rarely emphasizes the benefits of the product, but focuses instead on storytelling. <br data-mce-fragment="1"><br data-mce-fragment="1">The brand’s momentum on TikTok began two days before the product even launched when a video of Zaver and Perez giving samples around Minneapolis went viral. That initial interest led to the first batch of inventory selling out in a month.  <br data-mce-fragment="1"><br data-mce-fragment="1">“We honestly had no clue how fast it would sell,” Zaver said. “I was honestly thinking anywhere between like five and six months.” <br data-mce-fragment="1"><br data-mce-fragment="1">When it came time to replenish that initial 14-pallet shipment, which was delivered to Zaver’s parents’ house, the pair learned they were facing a four-month lead time. Instead of immediately opening shop again for pre-orders, Perez said they took those four months to learn and make adjustments. <br data-mce-fragment="1"><br data-mce-fragment="1">One of those adjustments was the decision to move operations out of his parents’ basement and into a warehouse in Plymouth. Since making the move, they’ve already sold out of a 38-pallet shipment and are now expecting 150 more pallets in the next month. <br data-mce-fragment="1"><br data-mce-fragment="1">Zaver said Seeq’s followers think it's selling out so quickly to demonstrate scarcity and build more buzz around the product, but he promises supply-chain delays are to blame.<br data-mce-fragment="1">“We could not be ordering more,” he said. “We’re ordering like hundreds of thousands of pounds. But I think in the next four or five months we will finally be caught up.” <br data-mce-fragment="1"><br data-mce-fragment="1">The powder is produced by a turnkey manufacturer in Wisconsin that does everything from sourcing ingredients to packaging the 1.5-pound bottles. <br data-mce-fragment="1"><br data-mce-fragment="1">Looking ahead, Zaver and Perez said it would be easy to not change anything about their business model, but they plan to start selling on Amazon at the end of the year.</span>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
