<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://seeqsupply.com/blogs/new-watermelon-wave-recipes.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://seeqsupply.com/blogs/new-watermelon-wave-recipes"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://seeqsupply.com/blogs/new-watermelon-wave-recipes/tagged/jello-mixed-berry-protein.atom"/>
  <title>SEEQ  - NATIONAL WATERMELON DAY RECIPES</title>
  <updated>2024-08-01T17:12:30-05:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>SEEQ </name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://seeqsupply.com/blogs/new-watermelon-wave-recipes/clear-protein-jello</id>
    <published>2024-08-01T17:12:30-05:00</published>
    <updated>2024-09-16T15:30:36-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://seeqsupply.com/blogs/new-watermelon-wave-recipes/clear-protein-jello"/>
    <title>Clear Protein Jello</title>
    <author>
      <name>Jake Hoffman</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[Ready to get jigg(ly) with it? Dive into our clear protein jello recipe for a delicious, high-protein, low-sugar snack that supports your health and wellness goals. Learn how to make it step-by-step and discover tips for perfecting your jello every time.<p><a class="read-more" href="https://seeqsupply.com/blogs/new-watermelon-wave-recipes/clear-protein-jello">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<h2 data-mce-fragment="1">Clear Protein Jello</h2>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">Ready to get jigg(ly) with it? Our clear protein jello recipe is here to satisfy your cravings while supporting your health and wellness goals. Whether you're after a guilt-free dessert or a tasty boost to your daily protein intake, this protein-packed jello is low in sugar, full of flavor, and your new go-to snack. With its numerous benefits and easy preparation, it’s a perfect addition to any diet. Try this clear protein jello with any of our SEEQ juicy flavors, and be sure to check out the tips and tricks at the bottom of the page.</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"><img src="https://cdn.shopify.com/s/files/1/0557/2345/8749/files/Clear_Protein_Jello_480x480.png?v=1722550339" alt=""></p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1"> </p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">INGREDIENTS:</p>
<ul data-mce-fragment="1">
<li data-mce-fragment="1">1 scoop of SEEQ Watermelon Wave Clear Whey Protein Isolate (or your favorite flavor)</li>
<li data-mce-fragment="1">8 oz of cold water</li>
<li data-mce-fragment="1">8 oz of boiling water</li>
<li data-mce-fragment="1">2 packs of gelatin (1/2 oz) or 1 package of any flavored Jello mix</li>
</ul>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">INSTRUCTIONS:</p>
<ol data-mce-fragment="1">
<li data-mce-fragment="1">Combine cold water and 1 scoop of your favorite SEEQ Clear Whey Protein flavor in a shaker and shake thoroughly.</li>
<li data-mce-fragment="1">Pour 8 oz of boiling water into a heat-proof dish or large heat-proof measuring cup (if you're making individual Jello servings).</li>
<li data-mce-fragment="1">Add the gelatin to the boiling water and stir until dissolved.</li>
<li data-mce-fragment="1">Strain your SEEQ protein into the gelatin mixture and stir gently.</li>
<li data-mce-fragment="1">Place the dish into the fridge or, if making individual servings, slowly pour the mixture into glasses.</li>
<li data-mce-fragment="1">Refrigerate for 4 hours or until set</li>
</ol>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">TIPS &amp; TRICKS:</p>
<ul data-mce-fragment="1">
<li data-mce-fragment="1"><em data-mce-fragment="1">If you are looking to up this clear protein jello recipe with 39 grams of protein instead of 22 grams — use beef gelatin in place of regular gelatin. Not only are you going to be benefiting from the extra protein but beef gelatin is also packed with collagen!</em></li>
<li data-mce-fragment="1"><em data-mce-fragment="1">Mix the SEEQ Clear Whey Protein with cold water before adding it to the gelatin mixture to prevent clumps.</em></li>
<li data-mce-fragment="1"><em data-mce-fragment="1">To get in your daily fruit servings, try adding some cut-up fruit into your jello molds for delightful added flavor and nutrition.</em></li>
<li data-mce-fragment="1"><em data-mce-fragment="1">To add a bit of fun and creativity, consider using jello molds. You can find a variety of molds on Amazon or at your local store to suit your taste and style!</em></li>
</ul>
<!-- notionvc: 4141ac0f-5580-4dbf-93d2-79e2140e0053 -->]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
